[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "And you call me up again just to break me like a promise, so casually cruel in the name of bein' honest, I'm a crumpled-up piece of paper lyin' here",
        "option1": "Cornelia Street",
        "option2": "All Too Well",
        "option3": "Red",
        "answer": "All Too Well",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/tollGa3S0o8"
    },

     {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "One for the money, two for the show, I never was ready so I watch you go, sometimes you just don't know the answer 'til someone's on their knees and asks you",
        "option1": "Champagne Problems",
        "option2": "Gold Rush",
        "option3": "Willow",
        "answer": "Champagne Problems",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/wMpqCRF7TKg"
    },

     {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I knew you'd haunt all of my what-ifs, the smell of smoke would hang around this long, 'cause I knew everything when I was young",
        "option1": "Tolerate It",
        "option2": "The 1",
        "option3": "Cardigan",
        "answer": "Cardigan",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/K-a8s8OLBSE"
    },

     {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "You were my crown, now I'm in exile seein' you out, I think I've seen this film before so I'm leaving out the side door",
        "option1": "Exile",
        "option2": "The 1",
        "option3": "Look What You Made Me Do",
        "answer": "Exile",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/osdoLjUNFnA"
    },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Please picture me in the weeds, before I learned civility, I used to scream ferociously any time I wanted",
        "option1": "August",
        "option2": "Seven",
        "option3": "Betty",
        "answer": "Seven",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/pEY-GPsru_E"
    },

     {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Losing him was blue like I'd never known, missing him was dark gray, all alone (Whoa)",
        "option1": "Stay Stay Stay",
        "option2": "Red",
        "option3": "State of Grace",
        "answer": "Red",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/R_rUYuFtNO4"
    },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "All we are is skin and bone trained to get along",
        "option1": "Treacherous",
        "option2": "Begin Again",
        "option3": "Red",
        "answer": "Treacherous",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/u1D1AgDfreg"
    },

    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "We're happy, free, confused, and lonely at the same time, it's miserable and magical oh yeah... tonight's the night when we forget about the deadlines, it's time oh-oh",
        "option1": "Holy Ground",
        "option2": "Lover",
        "option3": "22",
        "answer": "22",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9boiT64sm0Q"
    },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Life was a willow and it bent right to your wind but I come back stronger than a '90s trend",
        "option1": "The Last Great American Dinasty",
        "option2": "Willow",
        "option3": "Ronan",
        "answer": "Willow",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/RsEZmictANA"
    },

    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "While you were out building other worlds, where was I? Where's that man who'd throw blankets over my barbed wire? I made you my temple, my mural, my sky",
        "option1": "Mad Woman",
        "option2": "Tolerate It",
        "option3": "Miss Americana & The Heartbreak Prince",
        "answer": "Tolerate It",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/ukxEKY_7MOc"
    },

    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "And when we had that fight out in the rain, you ran after me and called my name, I never wanna see you walk away",
        "option1": "You Need To Calm Down",
        "option2": "I Bet You Think About Me",
        "option3": "Me!",
        "answer": "Me!",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/FuXNumBwDOM"
    },

    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "With your organic shoes and your million-dollar couch I bet you think about me when you say 'Oh my god, she's insane, she wrote a song about me'",
        "option1": "I Bet You Think About Me",
        "option2": "Sad Beautiful Tragic",
        "option3": "Everything Has Changed",
        "answer": "I Bet You Think About Me",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/5UMCrq-bBCg"
    },

    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "I bet this time of night, youâ€™re still up, I bet you're tired from a long hard week, I bet you're sittin' in your chair by the window looking out at the city",
        "option1": "Cruel Summer",
        "option2": "Daylight",
        "option3": "I Almost Do",
        "answer": "I Almost Do",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/w1AV_35zVwU"
    },

    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "You heard the rumors from Inez, you can't believe a word she says, most times, but this time it was true",
        "option1": "Invisible String",
        "option2": "Illicit Affairs",
        "option3": "Betty",
        "answer": "Betty",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/6TAPqXkZW_I"
    },

    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Oh, he's so smug, Mr. 'Always Wins', so far above me in every sense, so far above feeling anything",
        "option1": "We Were Happy",
        "option2": "Mr. Perfectly Fine",
        "option3": "Don't You",
        "answer": "Mr. Perfectly Fine",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/rFjJs6ZjPe8"
    },

     {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "That's when, when it's sunny or storming, when I'm laughing, when I'm crying, that's when I'll be waiting at the front gate",
        "option1": "Bye Bye Baby",
        "option2": "You All Over Me",
        "option3": "That's When",
        "answer": "That's When",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/aOa6D6ku3dM"
    },

    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "I was a dreamer before you went and let me down, now it's too late for you and your white horse to come around",
        "option1": "That's When",
        "option2": "White Horse",
        "option3": "Fairytale",
        "answer": "White Horse",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9-rKvhsjwKU"
    },

     {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "I'm standing there on a balcony in summer air see the lights, see the party, the ball gowns",
        "option1": "Hey Stephen",
        "option2": "Love Story",
        "option3": "Fifteen",
        "answer": "Love Story",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/aXzVF3XeS8M"
    },

    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Oh, I remember you driving to my house in the middle of the night, I'm the one who makes you laugh when you know you're 'bout to cry",
        "option1": "Tell Me Why",
        "option2": "Fearless",
        "option3": "You Belong With Me",
        "answer": "You Belong With Me",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/vwp8Ur6tO-8"
    },

    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "'Cause I don't know how it gets better than this, you take my hand and drag me head first, fearless",
        "option1": "Fearless",
        "option2": "Breathe",
        "option3": "You're Not Sorry",
        "answer": "Fearless",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/7lLigiVgJsE"
    },

    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "And I love you for giving me your eyes, for staying back and watching me shine, and I didn't know if you knew so I'm taking this chance to say that I had the best day with you today",
        "option1": "The Best Day",
        "option2": "Forever & Always",
        "option3": "Jump Then Fall",
        "answer": "The Best Day",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/KZeI9I875Ig"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "It feels like one of those nights, we ditch the whole scene. It feels like one of those nights, we won't be sleepin'",
        "option1": "Come Back... Be Here",
        "option2": "22",
        "option3": "I Knew You Were Trouble",
        "answer": "22",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9boiT64sm0Q"
    },

    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Paper cut stings from our paper-thin plans. My time, my wine, my spirit, my trust, tryna find a part of me you didn't take up",
        "option1": "Afterglow",
        "option2": "Cornelia Street",
        "option3": "Death By A Thousands Cuts",
        "answer": "Death By A Thousands Cuts",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/GTEFSuFfgnU"
    },

     {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "We were a fresh page on the desk filling in the blanks as we go, as if the street lights pointed in an arrow head leading us home",
        "option1": "Cornelia Street",
        "option2": "Death By A Thousands Cuts",
        "option3": "Daylight",
        "answer": "Cornelia Street",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/VikHHWrgb4Y"
    },

       {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "But I've learned a lesson that stressin' and obsessin' 'bout somebody else is no fun and snakes and stones never broke my bones",
        "option1": "Paper Rings",
        "option2": "You Need To Calm Down",
        "option3": "Cruel Summer",
        "answer": "You Need To Calm Down",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dkk9gvTmCXY"
    },

    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "I'm so sick of running as fast as I can wondering if I'd get there quicker if I was a man",
        "option1": "The Man",
        "option2": "The Archer",
        "option3": "Lover",
        "answer": "The Man",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/AqAJLh9wuZ0"
    },

    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "And there's a dazzling haze, a mysterious way about you, dear. Have I known you twenty seconds or twenty years?",
        "option1": "The Man",
        "option2": "The Archer",
        "option3": "Lover",
        "answer": "Lover",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/-BjZmE2gtdo"
    },

     {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "But I can see us lost in the memory, August slipped away into a moment in time 'cause it was never mine",
        "option1": "August",
        "option2": "Seven",
        "option3": "Style",
        "answer": "August",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/nn_0zPAfyo8"
    },

     {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Does a scorpion sting when fighting back? They strike to kill, and you know I will, you know I will",
        "option1": "This Is Me Trying",
        "option2": "Epiphany",
        "option3": "Mad Woman",
        "answer": "Mad Woman",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/6DP4q_1EgQQ"
    },

     {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Does a scorpion sting when fighting back? They strike to kill, and you know I will, you know I will",
        "option1": "This Is Me Trying",
        "option2": "Epiphany",
        "option3": "Mad Woman",
        "answer": "Mad Woman",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/6DP4q_1EgQQ"
    },

    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Oh, I can't stop you putting roots in my dreamland, my house of stone, your ivy grows and now I'm covered in you",
        "option1": "Ivy",
        "option2": "Coney Island",
        "option3": "'Tis The Damn Season",
        "answer": "Ivy",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9nIOx-ezlzA"
    },

    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "And I've cleaned enough houses to know how to cover up a scene. Good thing Este's sister's gonna swear she was with me",
        "option1": "No Body, No Crime",
        "option2": "Delicate",
        "option3": "'Evermore",
        "answer": "No Body, No Crime",
        "lyricsVideo": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/IEPomqor2A8"
    }
]